export const data = [
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Hurry Up'",
        option1: "Bʌsər",
        option2: "Rʌ Fɔy",
        option3: "KeKe",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Peanut'",
        option1: "Mɔt",
        option2: "Mʌ Kʌntər",
        option3: "Ro Kaŋ",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Provinces'",
        option1: "Ro Gbaŋ",
        option2: "Po",
        option3: "Beki",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Sit Down'",
        option1: "Kʌ Tis",
        option2: "Yirʌ",
        option3: "Kʌ Bo",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'I’ll be back	'",
        option1: "Kʌ Swit",
        option2: "Sɛkɛ",
        option3: "I Tə Kʌl Der",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'I am going home'",
        option1: "I Kɔnɛ Ro Seth",
        option2: "Man",
        option3: "Kʌ Gbara",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Mouth'",
        option1: "Uman",
        option2: "Kʌ Səŋ",
        option3: "Wath Bɛra",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'I am on my way'",
        option1: "Ashɔbi",
        option2: "Mari",
        option3: "I yi rə roŋ",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Onions'",
        option1: "Kʌ Fənt",
        option2: "Kʌ Yaba",
        option3: "Krep",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Tomorrow'",
        option1: "Ninʌŋ",
        option2: "Wath runi",
        option3: "Yathri",
        ans: 1
    },
    
]